kmall24.jp 2018-09-02

# privacy-policy - KMALL24

This privacy policy sets out how Kmall24 uses and protects any information that you give Kmall24 when you use this website. Kmall24 is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement and the site Terms and Conditions. Kmall24 may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

## WHAT WE COLLECT

We may obtain personal information about you from various sources, including this and other Kmall24 websites, mobile applications, when you email us or communicate with us through social media, or when you participate in events or other promotions.

  * Contact information (including name and email address)
  * Shipping information (including the shipping address and phone number)
  * Information you provide by interacting with us through social media, including photographs
  * Payment details (including payment card number, security code, expiration date, cardholder name and billing address)
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

## WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Process a transaction.
  * Provide products or services you request.
  * Improve our website and stores
  * Marketing and promotional purposes.
  * Enhance your shopping experience and so on.

We may share your information within KITA and third parties with whom we have a relationship for better customer services  
(ex. Logistics, Payment, etc.)

## SECURITY

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## HOW WE USE COOKIES

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at **help@kmall24.com**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
